expo-max.com 2013-11-25

# expo-MAX Privacy Policy

  |  |    
|  |   
| 

|   
---  
**General Provisions** expo-MAX Inc. takes strong measures to protect the security of your personal information. We take stringent precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration or destruction. We do not sell or give away personal information obtained from our advertisers or publishers. We collect different types of personal and other information based on your use of our products and services and our business relationship with you. All personal information is transferred from your browser to our server via Secure Server Layer (SSL) protocol and is stored using military grade 256-bit encryption algorithm with a strong 64-digit randomly generated password. We follow top tier industry standards to protect personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. **We collect information in the following ways** : You enter it yourself when you purchase or interact with us about a product or service we offer or provide;  
Via advertisement serving and tracking codes that you install on your website;  
Automatically when you visit our web sites or use our products and services. We use "cookies" (small files placed on your hard drive) on most of our pages to help analyze our web page flow, content and advertising, promotional effectiveness, as well as security. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although doing so may disable some of our website's functions. **We use the information we collect in a variety of ways, including to** : Provide you with the customer and technical support services;  
Process transactions/orders;  
Provide the services you purchase, and to respond to your questions;  
Communicate with you regarding service updates, offers, and promotions;  
Deliver customized content and advertising that may be of interest to you;  
Investigate, prevent or take action regarding any illegal activities. You can see, review and change some of your personal information by signing into your Advertiser/Publisher account at expo-MAX Control Panel. Generally, we do not manually modify your personal information. Also, you may not change any billing or credit card information related to a particular order/payment once the order is processed already. Your account on expo-MAX server is protected by a login and password pair for your privacy and security. You need to ensure unauthorized access to your account and personal information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by logging out after you have finished accessing your account. We operate our online services in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and do not permit registration by, and will not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from, anyone under 13 years of age. expo-MAX may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. If we make changes in the way we use personal information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Website. You can send us questions or feedback on any of our privacy policies.   
[](http://www.addthis.com/bookmark.php?v=250&username=xa-4c2b7e5d7c88cb51) expo-Max™ Home | Advertiser Solutions | Publisher Solutions | Website Traffic Statistics | [Web Search](http://search.expo-max.com/) | [Refile File Hosting](http://refile.net/) | [Zip Code Atlas](http://zipatlas.com/) | [DNS Tools](http://e-dns.org/) | [Trade Show Displays](http://showdisplays.ca/)   
News | Documentation | Frequently Asked Questions | Screenshots | [expo-MAX on Twitter](http://twitter.com/expoMAX) | Terms of Service | Privacy Policy | Refund Policy | Contact

Copyright © 2013 expo-Max Inc.  
All rights reserved. 

expo-Max and its derivatives are a property of expo-Max Inc. and may not be used   
without writtent permission or consent of expo-Max Inc. This site is PCI compliant with: | This site supports the following browsers:  
---|---  
|  |  |  |  |  |  |   
| **Firefox** | **Safari** | **Chrome** | Explorer | Netscape | Opera
